ENEA GUIDI

WEB3 DEVELOPER

+39 333 500 5981 guidi.enea@gmail.com × its-hmny.github.io San Marino, Italy

OVERVIEW

Fullstack developer with 2 years of professional experience working on over 4 projects in a wide range of categories and technology stacks. Managing already well established projects, as well as designing and implementing new ones from the ground up. I lead a team of 3+ people, by prioritizing and managing the development tasks. I'm a strong team player, always keen on improving myself and receiving feedback from my peers.

JOB EXPERIENCE

WEB3 DEVELOPER

Moonia s.r.l. / February 2022 - Today

San Marino 9

Design and implementation of a scripts suite aimed at facilitating NFTs generation and minting, as well as a Web3 SaS webapp to collect and manage NFTs project community data.

- Worked with Ethereum and Solana
- Automated Smart Contract deploy
- Focus on cost effectiveness
- Completely modular architecture

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

BOTIKA s.r.l. / March 2021 - Today

San Marino 9



Implementation of a webapp for digital fairs creation and management during the Covid-19 pandemic, using the MERN stack and Typescript.

- Both national and international fairs
- Focus on accessibility, i18n and UX
- 7.000+ online simultaneous users
- Third party services integration

PROJECTS

CHOREIA

Bachelor's degree thesis project, a static analysis tool that associates to a concurrent Go program its respective Choreography Automata.

- Proof of Concept
- Static Analysis
- Choreography Automata

3D CELLULAR AUTOMATA

A 3D playground to tweak and interact with Cellular Automata simulation.

- three.is
- React
- Typescript

MY PANTRY PAL

Hybrid mobile app that allows the user to manage their pantry and grocery lists, keeping also track of the available groceries at any given time.

- Ionic
- React
- Typescript

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022

BSc in Computer Science

University of Bologna | Italy

Graduated in March 2022 with final evaluation of 108/110, GDA (27/30)

TECHNOLOGIES

React/Next.js	
Express/Nest.js	
PostgreSQL	
Hardhat/Web3.is	

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Typescript	
Python	
Go	
C/C++	

LANGUAGES

Italian	
English	
German	